[
    {
        "id": "1bc2bd22-52e8-429a-ac43-5a9354336d03",
        "title": "Hiragana 1",
        "questions": [
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "i",
                "answer": "い",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "ち", "に", "さ", "ん", "よ"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "chi",
                "answer": "ち",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "い", "に", "さ", "ん", "よ"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "ni",
                "answer": "に",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "い", "ち", "さ", "ん", "よ"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "sa",
                "answer": "さ",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "い", "ち", "に", "ん", "よ"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "n",
                "answer": "ん",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "い", "ち", "に", "さ", "よ"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "yo",
                "answer": "よ",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "い", "ち", "に", "さ", "ん"
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "98f6645b-be63-4300-bfab-aa63ed938ca3",
        "title": "Hiragana 2",
        "questions": [
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "ro",
                "answer": "ろ",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "く", "な", "あ", "お", "き"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "ku",
                "answer": "く",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "ろ", "な", "あ", "お", "き"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "na",
                "answer": "な",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "ろ", "く", "あ", "お", "き"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "a",
                "answer": "あ",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "ろ", "く", "な","お", "き"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "o",
                "answer": "お",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "ろ", "く", "な", "あ", "き"
                ]
            },
            {
                "prompt": "Select the correct characteer(s) for:",
                "subject": "ki",
                "answer": "き",
                "wrongAnswers": [
                    "ろ", "く", "な", "あ", "お"
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
]
